[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 35]
Why did you summon the Bone-Corroding Harp?
The Bone-Corroding Harp?
I didn't summon it.
Could it be
it thinks
I've become the Demon Queen?
You won't be the Demon Queen.
Luo Ning,
the merging wine you just drank
was made from the Phoenix Tears.
It will make you forget
all the people
and things you love.
What did you say?
Forget all the people and things I love?
Then I'll forget...
No.
Don't struggle to hold on.
You'll soon forget He Na.
You
have always been willful.
No.
You will never marry
a stranger, right?
No.
He Na should be here soon.
What's wrong with Mr. Tai?
I saw through
his scheme easily.
So I put
the tampered clothes
in a beautiful place.
And I just wait for my brother
to bring the people from the Immortal Palace
to step into the trap.
No.
Fu.
It's not He Na.
Stop doing bad things.
Luo Ning.
Forget He Na.
Let's start over.
Fu.
No.
Fairy Luo Ning,
although it's one day late,
I still want to wish you a happy birthday.
How about I be your brother?
I am
about 1,000 years old this year.
♫In the sea of clouds, I looked at the reflection of the moon in the water♫
General of Water,
how old are you?
I'm almost 1,000 years old.
Almost 1,000 years old?
♫I kept waiting and arched my palms into a circle♫
That means you haven't.
Call me sister.
Sister.
♫The reflection gradually reminded me of our first meeting♫
Fu.
You look ugly wearing this.
Whether you find a way or not,
♫I can no longer tell the difference between wind and rain♫
you have to promise me one thing.
Don't come back too late.
♫Even if I get the volley sword♫
Fu.
I don't want to forget.
I know you're bad.
♫I can't forget you♫
I know you've done a lot of bad things.
♫Our destiny has been sealed long ago♫
But I still don't want to forget you.
♫I have no other choice♫
Fu.
♫Why have you been so far away from me every time♫
♫For billions of years♫
♫Can I use your hands to warm up the world again?♫
No.
You're sure
that my feelings for you are real. -No.
♫A few hasty nights♫
From the beginning,
Fu.
all my feelings for you
are part of your plan, right?
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
Even you dislike me
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
because I am an aquatic monster
that will die without water, right?
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch And watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
From now on,
I don't want to see you again
♫The remaining flowers in the mirror reflect the moon in the water♫
No, Fu.
♫We can't live up to such a good time♫
♫Recalling the unforgettable glance at the beginning♫
No.
♫I realized that it was a thousand years ago♫
I can't remember.
I seem to remember
♫Is this bad luck, or good luck?♫
there's a boy who looks evil and handsome while smiling.
♫He said that responsibility and love are difficult to balance♫
He became a lunatic.
I want him to be normal.
♫He had no choice but to leave me♫
I did it for him.
I want to marry He Na.
I want to lift that eternal curse.
♫The past has passed, so do not linger♫
But who is that boy?
♫My love for you is still so strong♫
-Why can't I remember? -Luo Ning.
Luo Ning.
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
Who is that boy?
Who is he?
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
I don't want to forget him.
But I can't remember.
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch and watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
Who is he?
Luo Ning.
♫Life is like a grain of sand♫
♫It burns the fire in my heart♫
Luo Ning.
♫I want to burn myself to hear you say you have never changed♫
Luo Ning!
Luo Ning.
Luo Ning, wake up!
Luo Ning!
Your Majesty.
Follow my moss,
you will know
where General Fu is.
Protection Spell?
How is she?
General Fu,
Fairy is fine.
She's fine?
She has been in a coma
since she took the Phoenix Tears
How could you say she's fine?
Fairy is indeed fine.
And she's pregnant for three months.
You mean
Luo Ning is pregnant?
Three months?
Isn't that when we were together?
Luo Ning.
Can you hear me?
We have our own child.
Liu Shao.
Luo Ge.
Why didn't you take me along to find Luo Ning?
How can I rest assured
in the Immortal Palace?
Luo Ning has the Glazed Pearl I gave her.
I tried to feel it just now.
She doesn't seem to be nearby,
but in the northeast.
She's at least 100 miles away.
That is…
The Ice Rock Lake.
Ice Rock Lake?
Yes.
Liu Shao.
Isn't that the place where we found the Bone-Corroding Harp?
It's extremely unfavorable to the Melody race.
Why is Fu there?
Luo Ning.
You're awake.
Who are you?
[Happy]
Tell me.
What's your name?
My name is Fu.
You look nice.
But my brother is still more handsome.
You look
nice.
But my brother
is still more handsome.
You are just
slimmer.
Maybe too slim.
I'll gain weight.
You don't look like a good person.
But
you're quite interesting.
As long as I am interesting to you.
By the way,
why am I here?
I clearly remember that
I was
in the wedding with He Na.
When we were bowing,
he left for something suddenly.
And then...
And then what happened?
Something happened to my brother
so he asked me to bring you here.
Your brother?
So you're He Na's brother.
Yes.
That's strange.
Is there anything more important
than our wedding?
Did you
marry He Na
to lift the curse?
Yes.
That eternal curse
has hurt many Aquatic Demons.
It also hurt that...
that...
It hurt that...
I can't remember.
It hurt me.
It made me do a lot of bad things
that made you sad.
You don't want me to do bad things.
What are you talking about?
I don't know you at all.
What does it have to do
with me?
You really don't know me?
I've been in your room for so long.
Why didn't you drive me away?
Here is not the Immortal Palace,
nor my house.
Don't they look alike?
They do.
But
I feel something's wrong.
It seems
something is missing.
What is missing? Let me help you.
I know.
This is it.
This doll
is made of my clothes.
It means everything
-is from me. -Don't
give me this ugly doll.
Otherwise,
it will destroy
the feng shui of the Waterside Pavilion.
Do you remember this ugly doll?
Of course I do.
Before I got married,
♫I want to get close but I can't see clearly♫
I've packed it up.
This doll is so ugly.
♫Who arranged this rain?♫
Why did I bring it with me
when I got married?
It's strange.
If I don't take it with me,
♫I want to avoid but I meet you again♫
I feel like something is missing in my heart.
♫I can't help but stay with you♫
♫The stars call the morning sky♫
♫May you feel relieved♫
You...
How dare you be rude to me!
My brother and He Na
won't let you off.
♫I long for a hug♫
Even if they won't let me off easily,
♫Can I not just listen?♫
I don't want to let go of you anymore.
What's wrong with you?
♫I want to find our way through destiny♫
You bullied me just now.
Why did you...
♫I want to throw away the memory in exchange for you to come back♫
Nothing.
I just feel a little uncomfortable.
♫Raise the glass to reincarnate the world♫
Why are you hurt?
Seems that
it's burnt from the inside.
♫I'll wait for your response with no regrets♫
Does it hurt?
No.
Don't be afraid.
♫I'll find the promised home for you♫
I'm not afraid.
But
I think I can treat this kind of wound.
♫My heart aches and I will say yes again♫
♫When will we separate?♫
♫Please don't tell us our ending in advance♫
It really works.
By the way,
what's your name?
My name is Fu.
Fu?
I think
I did these things for you before.
You did.
Really?
But why
I can't remember?
Are we really close?
Not only are we close,
we are a real couple.
So you can't marry my brother.
I will beg my brother,
your brother,
and the people in the Immortal Palace
to agree to our marriage.
As long as I can be with you,
I'm willing to pay any price.
In the future,
we will have a lovely kid.
They have no reason to reject us.
But I really don't remember
anything you said.
F...
Fu.
No matter how much you said,
I have to ask my brother
what's going on first.
If it's really like what you said
♫The stars call the morning sky♫
that we love each other so much,
I wouldn't have
forgotten you for no reason.
♫May you feel relieved♫
I made many mistakes
that made you forget me.
♫I long for a hug♫
I'll ask your brother for forgiveness.
♫Can I not just listen?♫
From now on,
you won't hate me anymore.
You will fall in love with me
♫I want to find our way through destiny♫
and be willing to be with me again,
right?
♫I want to throw away the memory in exchange for you to come back♫
Will I fall in love with you
and be willing to be with you?
♫Raise the glass to reincarnate the world♫
Yes, you will.
Fu.
♫I'll wait for your response with no regrets♫
♫I'll find the promised home for you♫
Luo Ning.
I have something to do.
♫My heart aches and I will say yes again♫
Wait for me here.
You...
♫When will we separate?♫
You mean
leaving me here
and not letting me out?
When I come back,
♫Please don't tell us our ending in advance♫
I'll take you out.
I'll take you to
wherever you want.
But if
I can't come back,
your brother will take you out.
My brother?
Are you going to find my brother?
But you just said
you did many wrong things.
Will he kill you?
Maybe.
But since you don't remember me,
you won't be sad, right?
This glazed bead is made by me
♫I want to get close but I can't see clearly♫
by copying sutras for years.
It is said that
♫Who arranged this rain?♫
it can ward off evil and avoid disaster.
Take it.
Come back safely.
♫I want to avoid but I meet you again♫
♫I can't help but stay with you♫
Come back safely.
♫The endless mountains and seas condensed into raindrops♫
I'll wait for you here.
You've told me your name many times.
♫I have walked thousands of miles with the feeling of missing you♫
But I still can't remember.
Your name is…
♫I want to ask the prophecy where should I go♫
Your
♫For whom did the foreshadowing disappear?♫
name is...
is...
♫I want to find our way through destiny♫
♫I want to throw away the memory in exchange for you to come back♫
My name is Fu.
♫Raise the glass to reincarnate the world♫
♫I'll wait for your response with no regrets♫
♫I'll find the promised home for you♫
Fu.
♫My heart aches and I will say yes again♫
♫When will we separate?♫
♫Please don't tell us our ending in advance♫
Fu.
[Fu]
With this,
I won't forget.
Fu.
[Fu]
How is the Great Wilderness?
As you wish,
someone fell into the trap
in the center of the Great Wilderness.
That's right.
If they want to track me,
they need to sacrifice something.
Who fell into it?
Only the Demon King in White.
My brother?
Shouldn't him bring Luo Ge
and Wanwu
together?
On the contrary,
he went there alone
to distract them.
Probably because he's afraid that people from the Immortal Palace
will hurt you.
That place is extremely dangerous.
With my brother's cultivation,
will he be okay in there?
Luo Ge and the people from the Immortal Palace
will probably be induced to chase Luo Ning.
But we don't know
if they can save your brother.
Since Luo Ge is here,
I can't
involve in this matter.
What is that?
The Trap of Spiritual Power.
Demon King was trapped just now.
I wanted to save him.
But when I got close to that place,
my spiritual power became so uncontrollable
that I can hardly use magic.
I'm afraid this trap
was set especially for us by Fu.
Ge.
Didn’t you say Ning is not here?
It's none of our business that
He Na was tricked into the trap by his brother.
We don't have to take the risk for him.
Immortal Master,
He Na is my friend.
Now that he's in trouble,
I can’t stand by.
Shang Yurong,
the marriage is not completed.
There are a lot of unsettled issues
in the Immortal Palace and the Demon Palace.
Why don't you go out first?
Immortal Master can accompany me.
OK.
Be careful.
Okay.
Luo Ge.
I'm sorry.
He Na.
Didn't I remind you
not to protect Fu again?
But you hid his whereabouts on purpose.
These days,
I was busy with the wedding
and neglected him.
That's why he got the chance.
Luo Ge.
I'll try my best to find Luo Ning.
That's not what I want.
You must find Luo Ning.
The terrestrial aura here is weird.
It can confuse spiritual power.
This is the center of the Great Wilderness.
I didn't expect
Fu subdued the remnants of the eagle demons
and used this place to trap us.
Luo Ge.
I'll use the water energy
to block the terrestrial aura.
Break the encirclement of demons
and leave.
When Liu Shao and I
were hunted down by Ao Hen,
you protected us again and again.
Fine.
With the help of Immortal Luo Ge,
I don't believe
we can't break this trap.
What should we do?
Surround them.
The terrestrial aura here
is favorable to us.
The longer it takes,
the weaker they are.
They will come out sooner or later.
Stop.
Greetings,
Immortal Master.
You
have always been
unruly.
But after
you got your brother and Luo Ge into trouble,
you've become polite.
What are you up to?
You
are Luo Ning's elder.
It's reasonable for me
to be polite.
Luo Ning.
Don't mention Luo Ning to me.
Why did you get her involved
and ruin her marriage?
It's all my fault.
After I rescue my brother,
I will go to the Immortal Palace personally
to apologize.
Apologize?
You made their marriage into such a big joke.
Do you think you will be forgiven
by saying you're sorry?
Even if He Na, the Demon King,
will kneel down and apologize,
it depends on whether Immortal Luo Ge will accept it or not.
He can't even discipline his own brother.
I think
He Na can't be the Demon King anymore.
I'll make up my mistake at any cost.
I can even
give out my life.
But please don't insult my brother.
You stole your brother's marriage.
How dare you still pretend?
Immortal Master,
you've gone too far.
I didn't use all my strength.
How could he be hurt?
Kid.
You are too young
to fight me.
Luo Ning.
Where does the music come from?
Bone-Corroding Harp.
Luo Ning must be nearby.
Fu set a Protection Spell here.
Where is the entrance?
Crown Wheel,
take me to the entrance.
You know music well.
I want to give this harp to you
as your birthday gift.
Does it have a name?
It's made of the Love Wood
which is also known as the Bone-Corroding Wood.
That's why it's called the Bone-Corroding Harp.
Love
can corrode everything.
We can't know
if it's fortunate or unfortunate
to meet the one you love.
It's always a fortune
to meet.
But what if the ending is unfortunate?
As long as it's my choice,
whether
the result is good or bad,
I will not regret it.
The Protection Spell disappeared.
God of the Sun.
Ze Shui.
I...
Liu Shao.
I'm not Ze Shui.
I'm Luo Ning.
And I'm not the God of the Sun.
It must be the Crown Wheel and the Bone-Corroding Harp
that recalled the memories of Ze Shui and the God of the Sun.
Here is...
Look.
Is it the same as my old house?
It's that...
that...
Fu?
Yes.
He must have decorated this place.
It looks like he prepared it for me.
But I don't know why,
after he left,
I can't remember his face.
When he was by my side,
I couldn't remember his name.
I...
You don't remember him?
Use your water energy to resist the evil spirit.
I will use the Moon Sword
to break the encirclement of demons.
Okay.
You mean
that boy
and my brother
are all here.
Your brother and He Na
were lured here by Fu.
I'm afraid he set an ambush.
Fu set an ambush?
Is he going to do something bad again?
Again?
Why should I say "again"?
How many things had happened
between us?
Why can't I remember anything?
Immortal Master.
Fu.
Brother.
Immortal Master.
Ge.
Don’t let him go.
I didn't mean to hurt him.
He must have done this
because he's been corroded by evil things.
He may harm the three worlds
and the people at any time.
Nonsense!
How could he resist my evil spirit?
Ge.
Look.
The evil spirit.
Fu.
Go back with me first.
I don't want to do this.
But you forced me.
Fu!
Luo Ning.
You will be fine.
I'll save you right away.
Luo Ning.
Luo Ning!
Brother, don't…
don't kill him
and don't do useless healing.
[Fu]
Fu.
With this,
I won't forget.
No.
Luo Ning.
You should have forgotten me.
If you had forgotten me earlier,
this wouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry.
Luo Ning.
Fu.
I really
can't remember you.
But I really want to remember
what had happened
between us.
Many...
many things had happened between us.
Many things.
You're not good at crafting.
But
you deal with things quite interestingly.
Leave through here.
What if I don't come back?
If you don't come back,
I don't think I can do anything.
What are you talking about?
I mean you shouldn't fight again.
♫On rainy days, wind blows smoke♫
Even you dislike me
because I am an aquatic monster
♫Into circles♫
that will die without water, right?
You're not a monster.
♫On both sides, I'm chanting♫
♫The night is sleepless♫
Although
you are not a good person,
♫The shadows of the moon are incomplete, and people are in love♫
you're definitely not a monster.
♫A cocoon of shadows♫
Anyway, this curse
♫Your promise, my fate♫
has trapped our clan for ten thousand years.
No matter what it takes,
I will lift it.
No crooked ways.
♫In spring, seasons changed♫
OK.
♫But my heart is still the same♫
Anything you say.
No crooked ways.
Okay?
♫Back to the sky, the clouds passing by♫
But I still remember
♫Is like the things we went through♫
I've always
♫Beside the lake, on the boat♫
wanted to
♫The moment we passed each other♫
Luo Ning.
lift the curse for one person.
♫Can compare with the rest of my life♫
Is that
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
you?
Yes.
It's me.
♫Looking at your ageless face at the end of the world♫
But you don't have to do anything.
I just want you to be fine.
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can’t hear it♫
Ten thousand years…
♫When the flowers stop falling, you and I will miss each other♫
Ten thousand years of punishment
has been long enough.
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
♫After the missing, my face is still young♫
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
I,
the Ze Shui of ten thousand years ago,
♫If you see me for the first time in this life, I'll forever hold it in my heart♫
and the Luo Ning at present,
in the capacity of the Demon Queen,
am willing to forgive
♫Get lost in your sky♫
all members
♫Whose wilderness♫
of the
♫Clouds billow up and fade away in the four seas♫
Aquatic Demons,
as well as
♫The mountains and rivers after the farewell♫
the Demon King
of ten thousand years ago.
♫Silence♫
♫Time sighs silently♫
And
♫Whose passing years♫
Luo Ning.
the Fu
at present.
Luo Ning.
Brother.
Let him go.
Please...
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
Luo Ning.
Luo Ning!
♫Looking back at the love that still remains in your past life♫
Luo Ning.
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can’t hear it♫
♫When the flowers stop falling, you and I will miss each other♫
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
We can leave now.
♫Looking at your ageless face after deciding to spend the rest of our lives together♫
Really?
Yes.
That's great.
Is it that
the curse has been lifted?
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
♫ The year of my life fleets♫
♫Whose year is it♫
Luo Ning!